Well, I'm a certified investment
advisor. So, in this video, we'll go through
some training. So, let's start.
First, if we talk about that part,
here's the marking last Friday,
and that flat employment. After that, definitely
drop oil. And here we have a solid waste
oil. Compared to the Indian Rupee, it's at a
tremendous rate of 000, and it's
very high. It
can make its mark in the market. So,
you have 40% of the current price of Phase Malik here.
[Music]
But if you
talk about it long term, then today the developer here can
come into the market, so there's no doubt
that we would have made a profit. So, today you
can see half of the profit in dowry in this topic. Recently, Adani Group has been
provided with a right under estimate award for a solar deposit. So,
considering this, for the next twenty-five years, this solar
project is going to be entered here and
its commissioning can be seen from the third quarter onwards. So,
today
my notes in stock are convertible debentures.
Interest payment for, so today it has
launched above 6% through private placement by appointing its nodal officer
and find the match T20 score of this
in 2036 Yadav subsidiary has
entry in subscribe condition so if there is
any folding in it then you can place a stop loss of 98 with stop loss
finally if we talk about today and calendar
then today you will see traffic of
some blue chip companies like ASI Consumer Pimpal and ICICI Prudential
for Republic Day
photos because of this here
is the net profit of HDFC Bank but here which is ours
because here with a very sharp decline like
this video and
subscribe to the channel and
you will also see your member details below
here we will give
you swing positional and multibagger
stocks along with model portfolio till then meet
in the next video thank you